Guide to The Boys' Club of New York Records 1876-2002 MS 3000
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: Organizational Records
  - Subseries I.2: Board of Trustees
    - Subseries I.2.A: Board Minutes and related materials
      Minutes typically list meeting attendees and discuss nomination and elections of new members, obituaries and memorials for deceased members, and reports of the various board committees. Financial and operational matters are also frequently included, particularly matters relating to the various clubhouses and camps. There are some interesting references to membership issues, including ethnic and racial tensions and the changing demographics of the clubhouse neighborhoods, particularly in the 1950's and 1960's. There are also reports on clubhouse activities and special events. A list of "important items mentioned in Trustee minutes" through 1984, compiled by BCNY, is included in Box 6, Folder 6.
      There is some duplication of records in the Board of Trustee minutes, reflecting their original arrangement. In some instances (for example, in the 1940's), Executive Committee Minutes are included with board minutes.
      Note that access to Board of Trustee meeting minutes is restricted for 35 years from the date of creation. Materials that were subject to restriction at the time this finding aid was created are identified in the box and folder list.
      - Board Minutes, 1922-1926 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 5)
      - Board Minutes, 1927-1929 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 6)
      - Proposal for Lower East Side Branch, 1929 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 7)
      - Board Minutes, 1930-1935 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 8)
      - Board Minutes, 1936-1940 (Offsite-box 1, Folder 9)
      - Board Minutes, 1940-1947 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 1)
      - Board Minutes, 1948 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 2)
      - Board Minutes, 1949 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 3)
      - Board Minutes, 1944-1946 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 4)
      - Board Minutes, 1947-1949 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 5)
      - Board Minutes, 1950-1952 (Offsite-box 2, Folder 6)
      - Board Minutes, 1953-1955 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 1)
      - Board Minutes, 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 3)
      - Board Minutes, 1961-1962 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 4)
      - Board Minutes, 1963-1964 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 5)
      - Board Minutes, 1956-1958 (Offsite-box 3, Folder 2)
      - Board Minutes, 1965-1967 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 1)
      - Board Minutes, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 2)
      - Board Minutes, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 3)
      - Board Minutes, 1972-1973 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 4)
        Includes 1971 "Boys Club Special Report" with overview of programs and biographies of key staff members
      - Board Minutes, 1974-1976 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 5)
      - Board Minutes, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 4, Folder 6)
      - Board Minutes, 1979-1980 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 1)
      - Board Minutes, 1981-1984 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 2)
      - Board Minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2023), 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 3)
      - Board Minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2026), 1989-1991 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 4)
      - Board Minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2029), 1992-1994 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 5)
      - Board Minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2031), 1995-1996 (Offsite-box 5, Folder 6)
      - Board Minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2033), 1997-1998 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 1)
      - Board Minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2035), 1999-2000 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 2)
      - Board Minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2037), 2001-2002 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 3)
      - Board Minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2039), 2003-2004 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 4)
      - Board Minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2050), 2005-2015 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 5)
      - Important items mentioned in trustee minutes (Offsite-box 6, Folder 6)
      - Board Minutes -- Correspondence (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2033), 1997-1998 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 7)
      - Board Minutes -- Correspondence (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2035), 1999-2000 (Offsite-box 6, Folder 8)
      - Board Minutes -- Correspondence and drafts (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2036), 2000-2001 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 1)
      - Board Minutes -- Correspondence and drafts (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2037), 2002 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 2-3)
    - Subseries I.2.B: Trustee/Executive Files
      These files consist primarily of correspondence to and from Board members and executive staff, and are arranged by last name of the trustee or executive. Topics discussed include meetings, dinners, trustee responsibilities, recruitment and resignations, and pleas for funds. Files of executive staff, including Directors Peter Capra and Robert Olson, and Comptroller Robert Sisti, include information on staffing, employee operations, and other internal operations of the organization.
      - "A-BE", 1950's - 2001 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 4)
      - "BI-BL", 1990's - 2003 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 5)
      - "BO", 1960's - 1992 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 6)
      - "BR-BU", 1960's - 1999 (Offsite-box 7, Folder 7)
        Includes information on proposed merger with Flushing Boys' Club
      - "BU", 1960's -1985 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 1)
      - Campbell, Thomas; Campion, Frank, 1960's - 1998 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 2)
      - Capra, Peter, 1960's - 1970's (Offsite-box 8, Folder 3)
      - Capra, Peter: Memos to staff, 1957-1959 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 4)
      - Capra, Peter: Memorial Fund, 1964-1967 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 5)
      - Carhart, H. Whitfield; Clarke, Garvey E., 1970's - 1992 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 6)
      - "CO", 1970's - 1995 (Offsite-box 8, Folder 7)
      - Cromwell, Jarvis, 1960's - 1990's (Offsite-box 8, Folder 8)
      - "DA-DE", 1950's - 2003 (Offsite-box 9, Folder 1)
      - Deidrick, Arthur, 1990's (Offsite-box 9, Folder 2)
      - Doubleday, Nelson; Dunnington, Walter G., Jr., 1950's - 1970's (Offsite-box 9, Folder 3)
      - "E-F", 1970's - 1990's (Offsite-box 9, Folder 4)
      - "G", 1960's - 1990's (Offsite-box 10, Folder 1)
      - "H", 1930's - 1990's (Offsite-box 10, Folder 2)
      - Hallock, Gerard, 1959 - 1990's (Offsite-box 10, Folder 3)
      - Harriman, Roland, 1950's - 1970's (Offsite-box 11, Folder 1-2)
        Includes an interesting memorandum on the challenges faced by organizations like BCNY in "ghettos" such as Harlem
      - Ireland, Robert L., Jr., 1950's - 1980's (Offsite-box 11, Folder 3)
      - "I-M", 1950's - 1990's (Offsite-box 11, Folder 4-5)
      - Olson, Robert T., 1969-2002 (Offsite-box 12, Folder 1-3)
      - "P-S", 1980's - 1990's (Offsite-box 12, Folder 4)
      - Sisti, Anthony, 1950's - 1960's (Offsite-box 13, Folder 1)
        Includes the minutes of some Executive Staff Meetings. Additional staff meeting minutes will be found in Series II, Programs and Operations, Box 22, Folder 1.
      - Van Ingen, Herbert P., 1980's - 1990's (Offsite-box 13, Folder 2)
  - Subseries I.3: Board Committees
    This subseries includes minutes of Board Committee meetings as well as committee files with drafts, memoranda and correspondence relating to issues discussed at meetings.
    The Executive Committee was responsible for the day-to-day operations of the organization. The Committee met monthly and made recommendations to the Board of Trustees on major issues facing the organization. Minutes often include more detailed discussions of issues that are subsequently addressed in meetings of the Board of Trustees. They generally include summary reports from the other Board committees and from various members of the executive staff. Topics include budgetary and financial issues, clubhouse activities, building operations, expansion and divestments, camps, membership, events, and virtually every other aspect of BCNY administration.
    In 1916, a Ways and Means Committee was created to relieve BCNY's treasurer of sole responsibility for collecting current funds. In the early years, the Ways and Means Committee often met jointly with the Executive Committee, and minutes of its meetings are included with the Executive Committee minutes.
    The Administration Committee was formed in the early 1950's to provide coordination and oversight of the activities of the other committees, and to focus on long-term planning. Since the Administration Committee also assumed responsibility for oversight of executive operations, these files are a good source of information about personnel issues.
    The Finance Committee had responsibility for investments of funds. Minutes discuss fund performance, investment strategies, and related issues. Financial statements are frequently attached.
    The Education Committee files are concerned with BCNY's program to place members in private preparatory schools and colleges. This program was established in 1952 with money donated by trustee Victor Morawetz. Minutes discuss scholarships, IQ testing, selection of schools, and the performance of participants. There is also discussion of the placement of "Negro" boys.
    The Evaluation Committee was formed to assess the programs and activities of BCNY in the 1970's. Files include memoranda assessing BCNY's overall goals and challenges, which provide a detailed and interesting snapshot of the organization in the early 1970's.
    The Building Committees were responsible for supervising the activities and expenditures of their respective clubhouses. Files include descriptive information about the activities of both members and staff. There is also statistical information about membership and participation in programs, and analysis of the effects of ethnic, racial and social trends. There is some financial and budgetary information about the buildings as well.
    Note that access to Committee meeting minutes is restricted for 35 years from the date of creation. Materials that were subject to restriction at the time this finding aid was created are noted in the box and folder list.
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1917-1921 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1922-1924 (Offsite-box 13, Folder 4)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1925-1928 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 1)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1929-1930 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 2)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1931-1933 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1934-1936 July (Offsite-box 14, Folder 4)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1936 August - 1938 August (Offsite-box 14, Folder 5)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1939 September - 1939 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1940 (Offsite-box 14, Folder 7)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1941 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 1)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1942 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 2)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1943 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1944 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 4)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1945 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 5)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1946 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1947 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 7)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1948 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 8)
    - Executive Committee Minutes, 1954-1978 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 9)
    - Ways and Means Committee Minutes, 1953-1972 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 10)
    - Ways and Means Committee Minutes, 1973-1978 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 11)
    - Ways and Means Committee, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 1)
    - Administration Committee Minutes, 1952-1961 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 2)
      Includes organizational chart
    - Administration Committee Minutes, 1960-1968 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 3)
    - Administration Committee Minutes, 1968-1972 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 4)
    - Administration Committee Minutes, 1973-1976 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 5)
    - Administration Committee, 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 6)
    - Administration Committee, 1977-1981 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 7)
    - Finance Committee Minutes, 1967-1979 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 8)
    - Finance Committee Minutes, 1980-1984 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 1)
    - Finance Committee Minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2023), 1985-1988 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 2)
    - Personnel Committee Minutes, 1957-1979 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 3)
    - Education Committee Minutes, 1957-1967 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 4)
    - Education Committee, 1970-1977 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 5)
    - Education Committee, 1978-1982 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 6)
    - Nominating Committee, 1975-1980 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 7)
    - Pension Committee, 1980 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 8)
    - Pension Committee, 1980-1982 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 1)
    - Evaluation Committee, 1970-1982 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 2)
    - Evaluation Committee, 1973 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 3)
    - Jefferson Park Building Committee, 1959-1979 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 4)
    - Jefferson Park Building Committee, 1980-1982 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 5)
    - Joint Building Committee, 1952-1981 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 6)
    - Committees/Trustee lists, 1973-1981 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 7)
  - Subseries I.4: Women's Board
    The Women's Board was established in 1968. Its purpose was initially limited to managing BCNY's fund raising benefits, but eventually expanded to include administering volunteer programs such as Homework Help and R.E.A.D. Minutes date back to 1973 and are primarily concerned with planning of events, including Spring and Fall Dances, fashion shows, and movie and theater benefits. There is also some correspondence relating to meetings, events and volunteer programs, along with some financial statements.
    Women became eligible to serve on the Board of Trustees in 1989, and minutes and correspondence from the late 1980's include discussion of this issue.
    Note that access to Women's Board meeting minutes and related correspondence is restricted for 35 years from the date of creation. Materials that were subject to restriction at the time this finding aid was created are identified in the box and folder list.
    - Minutes, 1970-1973 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 1980-1985 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 3)
    - Minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2026), 1986-1991 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 4)
    - Minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2032), 1992-1997 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 5)
    - Minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2035), 1998-2000 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 6)
    - Financial Statements (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2037), 1981, 2001-2002 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 7)
    - Minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2036), 2001 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 2)
    - Minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2037), 2002 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2037), 2002 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 4)
    - Minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2038), 2003 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2038), 2003 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 6)
    - Minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2039), 2004 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2039), 2004 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 8)
    - Minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2040), 2005 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2040), 2005 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 10)
    - Minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2041), 2006 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2041), 2006 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 2)
    - Minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2043), 2007-2008 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2043), 2008 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 4)
    - Minutes of Nominating Committee (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2035), 1985-2000 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 6)
    - By-laws, 1985, undated (Offsite-box 21, Folder 7)
    - Memoranda, correspondence and other documents (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2034), 1980's - 1999 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 8)
- Series II: Programs and Operations
  This series contains documents relating to the operation of the clubhouses and of various specific programs administered by BCNY. It is arranged into the following five subseries:
  Subseries II.1, Meetings and Reports, contains minutes of staff meetings, strategic plans, and other papers relating to the general administration of BCNY.
  Subseries II.2, Dental Clinic, consists primarily of minutes of the Clinic's Board of Directors meetings.
  Subseries II.3, Education Program, contains reports, pamphlets, and articles relating to a scholarship program that places BCNY members in private preparatory schools and colleges, and to other literacy and vocational initiatives.
  Subseries II.4, Other Programs, includes materials relating to Athletic Program events, jobs and vocational programs, and health programs. In addition, this subseries includes materials describing BCNY's traditional "Group Club" model, under which boys organize into smaller groups or "clubs" headed by a staff member or volunteer group leader.
  Subseries II.5, Building Operations, includes materials relating to the physical operation of the clubhouses, as well as demographic information about the neighborhoods where they are located.
  - Subseries II.1: Meetings and Reports
    This subseries includes memoranda, reports and correspondence relating to staff meetings and organizational planning. Materials include detailed evaluations of BCNY programs and interesting descriptions of the communities in which they served.
    - Executive Staff Conference, 1964 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 9)
    - Trustee/Executive Staff meetings, 1970-1972 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 1)
      Related Archival Materials Note
      See also Subseries I.2.B, Trustee/Executive Files (Sisti, Anthony, Box 13, Folder 1).
    - "The Boys' Club of New York: It's Needs Today and in the Future", 1975 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 2)
    - Strategic plan, 1976-1977 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 2)
    - Clubhouse Director's Report, 2006 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 3)
  - Subseries II.2: Dental Clinic
    The Dental Clinic was incorporated in 1923 and eventually operated in each of BCNY's clubhouse buildings. This subseries includes meeting minutes, correspondence, and related materials describing the clinic's financial and medical operations.
    Note that access to Dental Board meeting minutes is restricted for 35 years from the date of creation. Materials that were subject to restriction at the time this finding aid was created are identified in the box and folder list.
    - Board minutes, 1923-1945 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 4)
    - Board minutes, 1946-1954 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 5)
    - Board minutes, 1955-1959 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 6)
    - Board minutes, 1960-1965 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 7)
    - Board minutes, 1966-1972 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 7)
    - Board minutes, 1973-1979 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 1)
    - Board minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2024), 1980-1989 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 2)
    - Board minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2030), 1990-1995 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 3)
    - Board minutes (RESTRICTED UNTIL 2037), 1996-2002 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 4)
    - Manual of Operations/By-laws/Presentation, 1979, 2006 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 5)
    - Regulatory documents, 1990's - 2000's (Offsite-box 23, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and articles, 1988-1999 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence and articles, 2001-2002 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 1)
  - Subseries II.3: Education Program
    This subseries consists primarily of reports, pamphlets and articles describing BCNY's Education Program. Established in the early 1950's with funds from former trustee Victor Morawetz, the program provides scholarships for members to attend prominent preparatory schools and colleges. Also included are materials relating to the summer school BCNY opened in 1985 in Bound Brook, New Jersey (Camp Northover, later renamed Camp Cromwell) and after-school literacy programs administered by the Women's Board.
    - Education Pilot Project - Survey of Tompkins Square Building, 1955 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 2)
    - History of Education Program, 1939-1941, 1981 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 3)
    - Education Program Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 4)
    - Education Program Annual Report, 1997-1998 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 5)
    - Education Program Annual Report, 1998-1999 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 6)
    - Education Program Annual Report, 1999-2000 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 7)
    - Education Program Annual Report, 2006-2007 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 8)
    - Education Program Bulletins and publications, 1964-2000 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 1-2)
    - Pamphlets, 1980's - 1990's (Offsite-box 25, Folder 3)
    - Mahoney Scholarship, 1981 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 4)
    - Dinner for Charles Sikoryak, Education Program Director, 1981 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 5)
    - Camp Northover School, Reports, 1984-1985 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 6)
    - Classroom, Inc., 1994 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 7)
    - After-School Literacy Programs: READ, 2006-2007 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 8)
    - Independent School Placement Program, 50th Anniversary, 2007 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 9)
    - Background articles on boys' education, 1960's, 2000's (Offsite-box 25, Folder 10-11)
  - Subseries II.4: Other Programs
    This subseries contains materials on various programs instituted by BCNY to serve their membership. It includes correspondence and ephemera relating to Athletic Program events, including two trans-Atlantic amateur boxing matches against the London Federation of Boys' Clubs in the 1950's; documents relating to BCNY's jobs program; documents relating to Saturday programming at the clubhouses; and applications for and descriptions of various programs aimed at promoting health and good character.
    There are also several folders of material (primarily memos and correspondence) regarding BCNY's "Group Club" program, which continues the approach introduced by first Superintendent Frances Tabor of organizing boys into small groups or "clubs" headed by a staff member or volunteer group leader. Group leaders are typically successful businessmen who serve as role models and mentors, including many BCNY trustees.
    - Athletics: London Boxing Tournament, 1952-1954, 1957 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 1-5)
    - Athletics: USA Abbe Swim Team Meets, 2007-2008 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 6)
    - Group Club/Volunteer Leaders Program, 1971-1999 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 7-8)
    - Jobs Program, 1981-1989 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 1-6)
    - Project B.O.L.D., circa 1998 (Offsite-box 27, Folder 6)
    - Saturday programs, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 1)
    - Ethics and Morality Program, 1989 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 2)
    - Health and Physical Fitness Program, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 3-4)
    - Health and Wellness Taskforce, 2006 (Offsite-box 28, Folder 5-7)
  - Subseries II.5: Building Operations
    This subseries includes documents relating to BCNY's various clubhouses, including title documents, proposals for branches, and construction and condition surveys. The branch proposals set forth building details and statistical information about the neighborhood supporting the need for BCNY's services, including demographics, density and prevalence of crime. There is also a folder of statistical reports providing detailed information about the membership and programs of the Jefferson Park Clubhouse in the 1980's.
    Access to documents relating to the construction of the Marion McMahon Abbe Clubhouse are restricted for 35 years from the date of creation, as noted in the box and folder list.
    - Title to 10th Street Property, 1888, 1899 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 1)
    - Proposed New Branch, East 111th Street, 1926-1929 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 2)
    - Plan for New Branch (Tompkins Square), 1928 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 3)
    - Statistical Reports, 1980-1985 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 4)
    - Proposal for Book/Game Room, 1981 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 5)
    - Construction Survey/Repointing repairs, Jefferson Park Clubhouse, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 6-7)
    - Condition Survey, Camp Northover, 1985 (Offsite-box 29, Folder 7)
    - Condition Survey, Tompkins Square Clubhouse, 1986 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 1)
    - Condition Survey, South Queens Boys and Girls Club, 1990 (Offsite-box 30, Folder 2)